所以,Rato,这节课我们学到了什么?
So, Rato, what have we learned in this lesson?
嗯,我学到了我不想写数据库和内容提供者。
>> Well, I learned that I do not want to write
你呢？
databases and content providers. What did you learn in this lesson?
嗯,J单元测试是很棒的，以及
>> Well, J unit tests are awesome, and building
建立我们的应用程序的后端框架是最光荣的工作
the back end framework of our apps is the
这是创建健壮的应用程序与伟大的用户体验
most glorious of work. It's an absolutely vital part
的一个绝对重要的一部分
of creating a robust app with a great user experience.
我也学到了Dan不能做一个英语口音
>> And I also learned that Dan cannot do an English accent.
幸运的是,您可以准备欢迎凯瑟琳回到第5课
>> [SOUND]. Fortunately, you can get ready to welcome back Katherine
那节课上我们将把activity组件拆成fragment组件
for lesson 5, where we'll shatter our activity into fragments, use
使用我们的内容提供者来填充更复杂的UI
our content providers to populate more complex UIs, and build layouts
以及构建在平板电脑上和手机上一样好的布局
that work as well on tablets as they do on phones.
这就好像方便的segway进入历史一样
>> Which seems like a convenient segway
也是android硬件的进化
into the history and evolution of Android hardware,